Berking, Max; Papers apap228
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Senate Bills, 1965; 2; 1.2 cubic ft.
  - Print. S. 3501, 5607, 5955, A.5404 / Intro. S. 3304, A.5174 - To Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Allowing School Districts to Expedite the Assessing of New Construction in Rapid-Growth School Districts, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 59)
  - Print. 3526 / Intro. 3302 - Creating a Temporary State Commission with Respect to the Apportionment and Districting of the State Legislature and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 60)
  - Print. 3566 / Intro. 3328 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Transportation for Emotionally Disturbed Children, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 61)
  - Print. 3567 / Intro. 3329 - To Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Awarding of Contracts; to Purchasing of Materials and Equipment; and to Rental of Road Machinery for Highway Purposes, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 62)
  - Print. 3568 / Intro. 3330 - To Repeal Section One Hundred Thirty-Two of the Highway Law, in Relation to Reports of Expenditure of County Road Fund Moneys, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 63)
  - Print. 3569 / Intro. 3331 - To Amend the Town Lawn, in Relation to Fire District Taxes, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 64)
  - Print. 3648 / Intro. 3377 - To Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Granting Partial Exemption from Taxation for School Tax Purposes, for the Real Property Owned by Certain Persons with Limited Income Who Are Sixty-Five Years of Age or Over, Undated (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 65)
  - Print. 3700 / Intro. 3429 - Changing the Corporate Name of Westchester Joint Water Works No. 1, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 66)
  - Print. 3701, 4453 / Intro. 3430 - To Amend the General Municipal Law, in Relation to Grievance Procedures for Employees of Political Subdivisions of the State Outside the City of New York and Repealing Subdivision Nine of Section Six Hundred Eighty-Four Thereof, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 67)
  - Print. 3745 / Intro. 3474 - To Amend the Civil Service Law, in Relation to Health Insurance for State and Retired State Employees, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 68)
  - Print. 3746, 5288 / Intro. 3475 - To Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to the Prevention of Excessive Noise of Motor Vehicles, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 69)
  - Print. 3790 / Intro. 3500 - To Amend the Civil Service Law, in Relation to Health Insurance for State and Retired State Employees, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 70)
  - Print. 3790 / Intro. 3500 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Residence Requirements for the Purpose of Qualifying for Examinations as Present Practitioners of Chiropractic in this State, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 71)
  - Print. 3810 / Intro. 3520 - To Amend Chapter Seven Hundred Twenty-Eight of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Fifty-Four, as Amended by Chapter Seven Hundred Thirty-Three of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Fifty-Seven Entitled "An Act in Relation to Continuing the City Court of New Rochelle, Defining its Powers and Jurisdiction and the Procedure Therein and Repealing Chapter Four Hundred Ninety-Nine of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Thirty-One, Entitled 'An Act in Relation to the City Court of New Rochelle'" in Relation to Creating Two Full-Time City Judges, Definitions, City Court Clerk, Interpreter, Stenographer, Marshal, and Deputy Marshal, Other Employees, Duties and Powers, Temporary Acting City Judge, Death or Removal of Judges, Juries, Criminal Jurisdiction, Small Claims and Jury Fees for Small Claims, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 72)
  - Print. 3959 / Intro. 3646 - To Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, in Relation to Retirement of Members of the Westchester County Parkway Police Force, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 73)
  - Print. 4233 / Intro. 3843 - To Repeal Section Fifty-Four-A, Section Fifty-Four-B, and Section Fifty-Four-C of the Railroad Law, Relation to Crews for Certain Trains, Engines, and Railroad Operations and to Provide Jobs Protection by Normal Attrition, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 74)
  - Print. 4257 / Intro. 3865 - To Repeal Subdivision Four of Section Four Hundred Fifty-Seven of the Public Authorities Law, Relation to Acquisition and Disposition of Real Property, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 75)
  - Print. 4276 / Intro. 3884 - To Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, in Relation to Retirement of Officers Who Are Transferees from Another Department of Force, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 76)
  - Print. 4277 / Intro. 3885 - To Amend Chapter Eight Hundred Fifty-One of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Forty-Nine, Entitled "An Act to Establish a Police Justice Court in the Village of Port Chester and to Repeal Chapter One Hundred Six of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Six, Entitled 'An Act Creating the Offices of Police Justice and Assistant Police Justice, in the Village of Port Chester, in the County of Westchester, and to Provide for Raising Annually an Amount Sufficient to Pay the Salaries of Said Officers,' Relating to Creating the Offices of Police Justice and Assistant Police Justice of the Village of Port Chester," in Relation to the Appointment of An Additional Village Marshal, and Repealing Section Sixteen-A of Such Chapter Relating to the Appointment and Duties of a Deputy Village Marshal, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 77)
  - Print. 4291 / Intro. 3899 - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly: Proposing an Amendment to Section Eight of Article Seven of the Constitution, in Relation to Providing that Legislature's Power to Authorize the Loan of Money of the State to a Public Corporation for the Purpose of Making Secured Loans to Non-Profit Corporations to Finance Construction of New Industrial or Manufacturing Plants in this State or the Acquisition, Rehabilitation, or Improvement of Former Industrial or Manufacturing Plants in this State Shall be Extended so as to Provide Improved Job Opportunities in any Part of the State, Rather than Only in the Areas of the State Where Unemployment Is or May Become a Critical Problem, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 78)
  - Print. 4331 / Intro. 3913 - To Amend The Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Venue in Actions Brought Against School Districts and District Corporations, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 79)
  - Print. 4394 / Intro. 3953 - To Amend the Agriculture and Markets Law, in Relation to Selling Preheated Bituminous Road Oil, Tar, and Allied Products by Net Weight to Any Municipal Corporation or Special District in the State of New York, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 80)
  - Print. 4395 / Intro. 3954 - To Amend the Education Law in Relation to Absentee Voting at School District Elections, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 81)
  - Print. 4396 / Intro. 3955 - To Amend the General Business Law, in Relation to the Manufacture of Refrigerators, Iceboxes and Similar Containers, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 82)
  - Print. 4397 / Intro. 3956 - To Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Additional Payments by State, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 83)
  - Print. 4938 / Intro. 3957 - To Amend the Personal Property Law, in Relation to Duty of Police to Keep Lost Property Having a Value of One Hundred Dollars or Less, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 1)
  - Print. 4399 / Intro. 3958 - To Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to the Abandonment of Motor Vehicles, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 2)
  - Print. 4400 / Intro. 3959 - To Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Traffic Regulations on County Roads, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 3)
  - Print. 4401 / Intro. 3960 - To Amend the Village Law, in Relation to Absentee Voting, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 4)
  - Print. 4495 / Intro. 4201 - To Amend the State Finance Law, in Relation to Payment of State Assistance to Westchester County Instead of to Certain Public Corporations in Which Railroad Property is Partially Exempt from Taxation, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 5)
  - Print. 4563 / Intro. 4089 - To Amend the General Municipal Law, in Relation to Commissions on Human Rights, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 6)
  - Print. 4564 / Intro. 4090 - To Amend the Local Finance Law, in Relation to Vote on Proposition for the Approval of a Bond Resolution or Capital Note Resolution, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 7)
  - Print. 4565 / Intro. 4091 - To Amend the Education Law, to Give the Trustees of the University of the State of New York the Power of Condemnation, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 8)
  - Print. 4566 / Intro. 4092 - To Amend the Education law, in Relation to Remedial, Psychiatric, Psychological and Social Work Services, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 9)
  - Print. 4567 / Intro. 4093 - To Repeal Subdivision Four of Section Four Hundred Fifty-Seven of the Public Authorities Law, Relating to Acquisition and Disposition of Real Property, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 10)
  - Print. 4568 / Intro. 4094 - To Amend the County Law to Provide for a Share of State Collected Taxes to Be Paid to Certain Counties for Providing Indigent Persons with Legal Assistance and Representation in Criminal Matters, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 11)
  - Print. 4646 / Intro. 4138 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Apportionment of Public Moneys to School Districts, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 12)
  - Print. 4668 / Intro. 4160 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Increasing the Maximum Award for Regents College Scholarships, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 13)
  - Print. 4669 / Intro. 4161 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Increasing the Number of Regents College Scholarships, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 14)
  - Print. 4694 / Intro. 4186 - To Amend the Banking Law, in Relation to Advertising of Interest Rates by Licensed Lenders and Prepayment of Loans Made by Licensed Lenders, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 15)
  - Print. 4695 / Intro. 4187 - To Amend the Banking Law, in Relation to Interest Charges by Licensed Lenders, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 16)
  - Print. 4696 / Intro. 4188 - To Amend the Multiple Dwelling Law, in Relation to Requiring Corporate Owners of Multiple Dwellings and certain Stockholders Thereof to File Names and Addresses of Shareholders in Certain Cases, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 17)
  - Print. 4697 / Intro. 4189 - To Amend the Military law and the Retirement and Social Security Law, in Relation to Retirement Benefits of Certain State Military Personnel, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 18)
  - Print. 4698 / Intro. 4190 - To Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to the Sale to Minors of Certain Pictures, Motion Pictures, Photographs, Books, Pamphlets, or Magazines, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 19)
  - Print. 4699 / Intro. 4191 - To Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to Possession of Antique Firearms, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 20)
  - Print. 4700 / Intro. 4192 - To Amend the Navigation Law, in Relation to Speed and Reckless Operation of Vessels, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 21)
  - Print. 4701 / Intro. 4193 - To Amend the Transportation Corporations Law, in Relation to Prohibiting the Discontinuance of Utilities in Multiple Dwellings, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 22)
  - Print. 4702 / Intro. 4194 - To Amend the General Corporation Law, in Relation to Filing names and Addresses of All Officers, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 23)
  - Print. 4703 / Intro. 4195 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to State Aid for Library Systems, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 24)
  - Print. 4704 / Intro. 4196 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Authorizing Pre-Kindergarten Programs, and Making Provisions Therefor in the Computation of Weighted Average Daily Attendance, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 25)
  - Print. 4704 / Intro. 4197 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Part-Time Enrollment in Public Schools, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 26)
  - Print. 4706 / Intro. 4198 - To Amend the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, in Relation to the Initial Issuance of a License to Sell Liquor at Retail Not to be Consumed on the Premises, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 27)
  - Print. 4707 / Intro. 4199 - Creating a Temporary State Commission to Study Consumer Credit Labeling in Terms of Simple Annual Interest, Make Recommendations in Connection Therewith, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 28)
  - Print. 4708 / Intro. 4200 - To Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to Empowering the State Commission for Human Rights to Eliminate and Prevent Discrimination in Mortgage Financing and the Insurance Business Because of Race, Creed, Color, or National Origin, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 29)
  - Print. 4709 / Intro. 4201 - To Amend the Insurance Law, in Relation to the Commission Payable Under a Plan for Assignment of Liability Insurance, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 30)
  - Print. 4710 / Intro. 4202 - To Amend the Insurance Law, in Relation to Extending the Section to Agents, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 31)
  - Print. 4711 / Intro. 4203 - To Amend the County Government Law of Nassau County, in Relation to Establishing Rules and Regulations for the Operation of Pleasure Vessels in Nassau County, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 32)
  - Print. 4712 / Intro. 4204 - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly: Proposing Amendments to Article Three of the Constitution, in Relation to the Number of Senators and Assemblymen and the Method of Creating Districts for their Election, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 33)
  - Print. 4713 / Intro. 4205 - To Amend the Judiciary Law, in Relation to State Aid to the Counties of Nassau and Suffolk for Certain Court Expenses, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 34)
  - Print. 4714 / Intro. 4206 - To Amend the Personal Property Law, in Relation to Retail Installment Contracts to Permit Cancellation by the Buyer, Prior to the Receipt of Goods and Services, for Failure of the Seller to Itemize the Amount of the Credit Service Charge, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 35)
  - Print. 4715 / Intro. 4207 - To Amend the Personal Property Law, in Relation to Retention of Fees by Attorneys, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 36)
  - Print. 4716 / Intro. 4208 - To Amend the Real Property Law and the Penal Law, in Relation to Requiring the Payment of Interest on Security Deposits under Leases of Real Property, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 37)
  - Print. 4717 / Intro. 4209 - To Amend the Public Health Law, in Relation to State Reimbursement of Expenditures by Counties and Cities, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 38)
  - Print. 4718 / Intro. 4210 - To Amend the Social Welfare law, in Relation to Liability of Relatives to Support Recipient of Public Welfare Assistance, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 39)
  - Print. 4719 / Intro. 4211 - To Amend Chapter Two Hundred Thirty-Six of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Fifty-Two, Entitled "An Act to Enable Certain Counties and Cities to Impose a Tax on Admissions to Running Horse Race Meetings and Providing for the Collection and Administration of Such Tax," in Relation to the imposition and Distribution of Such Tax on All Admissions, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 40)
  - Print. 5309 / Intro. 4469 - To Authorize and Empower the Village of Port Chester to Convey to the Port Chester Public Library a Portion of Certain Lands Acquired by the Village of Port Chester for Park Purposes, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 41)
  - Print. 5803 / Intro. 4649 - To Amend the Town Law, in Relation to the Adoption of a Town Manager Form of Government, and Defining Procedures Therefor and the Powers and Duties of Such Town Manager, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 42)